{
    "id": "ff8742a6ca5543fcaeb8ecd735c1f352",
    "title": "Confusing Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sam has ………………… on the bed all morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lain",
                "lied",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d9608b14555c4b31b9ebb50775ce593b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Alice says that she has already ………………… .. the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "laid",
                "lain",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d3a899c2ee24e94bcceacaa3a2e8bdc"
        },
        {
            "question": "The books were …………………… . on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "lain",
                "laid"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d8048eeb5fac413abf24160795ee5a5e"
        },
        {
            "question": "This time tomorrow I will be …………………. on the beach.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lying",
                "lieing",
                "lyeing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0a8de363f05e440db7ec5461dd8267f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "While ……………………… in bed, I had an idea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "laying",
                "lying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "965a2a0efaa34652af4e63aa75757c98"
        },
        {
            "question": "She always …………………… her books neatly on the table.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lays",
                "lies",
                "lains"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "aa55c02353554f399ae11b5ce169afec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t ………………… in bed all day.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lie",
                "lay"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9770f539c55446c4a3535f53dabd01ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. down and closed my eyes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lay",
                "lie",
                "lied"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "05d2faa29e474d2db7f28e674f35d1e0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I must be …………………. weight.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "losing",
                "loosing",
                "lousing"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a47a3091fe2d48d0b9f1928b57185c89"
        },
        {
            "question": "Did you …………………. cricket yesterday?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "practice",
                "practise"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "74e3a56e8c5f4949b37da16d5a8b8436"
        }
    ]
}